// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "What is perl?",
      answer: "Programming Language",
      options: [
        "Software",
        "Database",
        "Programming Language",
        "None of above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: " Perl is used for ______________",
      answer: "All of the Above",
      options: [
        "Text manipulation",
        "System Administration",
        "Web development",
        "All of the Above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Perl is developed by _____________",
      answer: "Larry Wall",
      options: [
        "Larry Wall",
        "Rasmus Lerdorf",
        "Guido van Rossum",
        "James Gosling"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Perl is written in which language?",
      answer: "C",
      options: [
        "C",
        "PHP",
        "Python",
        "Fortran"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Perl uses _____ operator to repeat a string.",
      answer: "x",
      options: [
        "x",
        "/",
        ".",
        "\\"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following function is used by perl for displaying the length of a string?",
      answer: "length",
      options: [
        "len",
        "split",
        "string",
        "length"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which function is used by perl for reversing a string?",
      answer: "reverse",
      options: [
        "rev",
        "split",
        "substr",
        "reverse"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following is the concatenation operator in perl?",
      answer: ".",
      options: [
        ".",
        "/",
        "_",
        "\\"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which extension is used to save a perl program files?",
      answer: ".pl",
      options: [
        ".sh",
        ".gp",
        ".pl",
        "None of above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following known as range operator?",
      answer: "..",
      options: [
        "$",
        "..",
        "$_",
        "$1"
      ]
    },
  ];